//Questions and Options array

const quizArray = [
 
  {
    id: "1",
    question: " Cauchy – Riemann equation is",
    options: ["ux = vy & uy = vy", "ux = vy & uy = vx", "ux = - vy & uy = vx", "ux = vy & uy = -vx"],
    correct: "ux = vy & uy = -vx",
  },
  {
    id: "2",
    question: "An analytic function with constant real part is",
    options: ["real", "imaginary", "constant", "neither real nor imaginary"],
    correct: "constant",
  },
{
    id: "3",
    question: "If f(z) = z3

then ux = ________",
    options: ["3x2 – 3y2","3z2","3y2 – 3x2","3x2 + 3y2"],
    correct: "3x2 – 3y2",
  },
{
    id: "4",
    question: "If f(z) = e-z

then vy =",
    options: ["- e
-x cosy","e
-x cosy","e
-y cosy","e
-x cosy"],
    correct: "- e
-x cosy",
  },
{
    id: "5",
    question: " If w = sin z then the value of vy is",
    options: ["vy = sinx coshy","vy = sinx sinhy","vy = cosx coshy","vy =- sinx coshy"],
    correct: "vy = cosx coshy",
  },
{
    id: "6",
    question: "A parentheses checker program would be best implemented using",
    options: ["List","Queue","Stack","Any of the above"],
    correct: "Stack",
  },
{
    id: "7",
    question: "If w=f(z) is not conformal at a point z0 ,where f ’

(z0) =0,then z0 is called",
    options: ["critical point","saddle point","vertical point","finite point"],
    correct: "critical point",
  },
{
    id: "8",
    question: "If given transformation isw=z-1/z+1 then fixed point is",
    options: ["-i","i","2","+ i"],
    correct: "+i",
  },
{
    id: "9",
    question: "If f(z) = u+iv is analytic,then u is said to be ________of v",
    options: ["conjugate harmonic", "harmonic function", "analytic function", "exponential function"],
    correct: "conjugate harmonic",
  },
{
    id: "10",
    question: "An analytic function with constant modulus is",
    options: ["variable","Constant"," Infinity","finite"],
    correct: " Infinity",
  },
{
    id: "11",
    question: "The cross ratio of (z1 ,z 2, z3, z 4) is defined as",
    options: ["(z4 –z1) (z3 – z2) / (z4 –z 3) (z 2– z1)","(z1 –z2) (z 3 – z4) / (z1 –z4) (z3 – z2)","(z2 –z3) (z1 – z4) / (z 3–z4) (z1 – z2 )","(z1 –z3) (z 2– z3) / (z1 –z2) (z 4– z 1)"],
    correct: "(z1 –z2) (z 3 – z4) / (z1 –z4) (z3 – z2)",
  },
{
    id: "12",
    question: "The image of y = 3x under w = 1 / z is",
    options: ["u – 3v = 0","3u + v = 0","u + 3v = 0","3u – v = 0"],
    correct: "3u + v = 0",
  },
{
    id: "13",
    question: "The critical point of w = z 2 is",
    options: ["1","0","2","-2"],
    correct: "0",
  },
{
    id: "14",
    question: "The image of | z + 1 | = 1 under the mapping w = 1/ z is",
    options: ["2u + 1 =0","1 – 2u = 0","2v +1 =0","1- 2v = 0"],
    correct: "2u + 1 =0",
  },
{
    id: "15",
    question: "The image of the circle | z | = 2 under the transformation w = 3z is",
    options: ["(u -3)2 + (v-3) 2 = 9","u 2 + v 2 = 3","(u -1)2 + (v-2) 2 = 4","u 2 + v 2 = 36"],
    correct: "u 2 + v 2 = 36",
  },

];